{
    "@type": "SpdxDocument",
    "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-DOCUMENT",
    "comment": "This document was created using SPDX 2.0 using licenses from the web site.",
    "creationInfo": {
        "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
        "createdBy": [
            {
                "actorType": "TOOL",
                "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
            },
            {
                "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
            },
            {
                "actorType": "PERSON",
                "name": "Jane Doe ()"
            }
        ],
        "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
        "profile": [
            {
                "name": "core"
            },
            {
                "name": "software"
            },
            {
                "name": "licensing"
            }
        ],
        "specVer": "3.0.0"
    },
    "elements": [
        {
            "@type": "Package",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-Package",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "description": "The GNU C Library defines functions that are specified by the ISO C standard, as well as additional features specific to POSIX and other derivatives of the Unix operating system, and extensions specific to GNU systems.",
            "downloadLocation": "http://ftp.gnu.org/gnu/glibc/glibc-ports-2.15.tar.gz",
            "homePage": "http://ftp.gnu.org/gnu/glibc",
            "name": "glibc",
            "originatedBy": [
                {
                    "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                    "name": "ExampleCodeInspect (contact@example.com)"
                }
            ],
            "packagePurpose": [
                "SOURCE"
            ],
            "summary": "GNU C library.",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "MD5",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "624c1abb3664f4b35547e7c73864ad24"
                },
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "85ed0817af83a24ad8da68c2b5094de69833983c"
                },
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA256",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "11b6d3ee554eedf79299905a98f9b9a04e498210b59f15094c916c91d150efcd"
                },
                {
                    "algorithm": "BLAKE2b384",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "aaabd89c926ab525c242e6621f2f5fa73aa4afe3d9e24aed727faaadd6af38b620bdb623dd2b4788b1c8086984af8706"
                },
                {
                    "algorithm": "packageVerificationCode",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "d6a770ba38583ed4bb4525bd96e50461655d2758"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "The File of that packages is",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": {
                "@type": "File",
                "SPDXID": "urn:File:00ecc9af0969f545c9a0f3dc3831b442",
                "creationInfo": {
                    "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                    "createdBy": [
                        {
                            "actorType": "TOOL",
                            "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                        },
                        {
                            "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                            "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                        },
                        {
                            "actorType": "PERSON",
                            "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                        }
                    ],
                    "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                    "profile": [
                        {
                            "name": "core"
                        },
                        {
                            "name": "software"
                        },
                        {
                            "name": "licensing"
                        }
                    ],
                    "specVer": "3.0.0"
                },
                "name": "glibc-2.11.1.tar.gz"
            },
            "relationshipType": "PACKAGES",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-Package"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:df339a5c07abcbefbca61116778b7481",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-Package",
            "relationshipType": "CONTAINS",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-Specification",
                "SPDXRef-Specification",
                "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
                "SPDXRef-Specification",
                "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
                "SPDXRef-JenaLib",
                "SPDXRef-Specification",
                "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
                "SPDXRef-JenaLib",
                "SPDXRef-DoapSource",
                "SPDXRef-Specification",
                "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
                "SPDXRef-JenaLib",
                "SPDXRef-DoapSource"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Package",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-fromDoap-1",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "homePage": "http://commons.apache.org/proper/commons-lang/",
            "name": "Apache Commons Lang"
        },
        {
            "@type": "Package",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-fromDoap-0",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "downloadLocation": "https://search.maven.org/remotecontent?filepath=org/apache/jena/apache-jena/3.12.0/apache-jena-3.12.0.tar.gz",
            "homePage": "http://www.openjena.org/",
            "name": "Jena"
        },
        {
            "@type": "Package",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-Saxon",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "description": "The Saxon package is a collection of tools for processing XML documents.",
            "downloadLocation": "https://sourceforge.net/projects/saxon/files/Saxon-B/8.8.0.7/saxonb8-8-0-7j.zip/download",
            "homePage": "http://saxon.sourceforge.net/",
            "name": "Saxon",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "85ed0817af83a24ad8da68c2b5094de69833983c"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "The File of that packages is",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": {
                "@type": "File",
                "SPDXID": "urn:File:029468bd5a7aa3b9aa185c90a9d111cc",
                "creationInfo": {
                    "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                    "createdBy": [
                        {
                            "actorType": "TOOL",
                            "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                        },
                        {
                            "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                            "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                        },
                        {
                            "actorType": "PERSON",
                            "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                        }
                    ],
                    "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                    "profile": [
                        {
                            "name": "core"
                        },
                        {
                            "name": "software"
                        },
                        {
                            "name": "licensing"
                        }
                    ],
                    "specVer": "3.0.0"
                },
                "name": "saxonB-8.8.zip"
            },
            "relationshipType": "PACKAGES",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-Saxon"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "File",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-DoapSource",
            "contentType": [
                "text/source"
            ],
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "name": "./src/org/spdx/parser/DOAPProject.java",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "2fd4e1c67a2d28fced849ee1bb76e7391b93eb12"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "File",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
            "comment": "This file is used by Jena",
            "contentType": [
                "archive/*"
            ],
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "name": "./lib-source/commons-lang3-3.1-sources.jar",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "c2b4e1c67a2d28fced849ee1bb76e7391b93f125"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "File",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-JenaLib",
            "comment": "This file belongs to Jena",
            "contentType": [
                "archive/*"
            ],
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "name": "./lib-source/jena-2.6.3-sources.jar",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "3ab4e1c67a2d28fced849ee1bb76e7391b93f125"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "File",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-Specification",
            "comment": "Specification Documentation",
            "contentType": [
                "text/documentation"
            ],
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "name": "./docs/myspec.pdf",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "fff4e1c67a2d28fced849ee1bb76e7391b93f125"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "File",
            "SPDXID": "SPDXRef-File",
            "comment": "The concluded license was taken from the package level that the file was included in.\nThis information was found in the COPYING.txt file in the xyz directory.",
            "contentType": [
                "text/source"
            ],
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "name": "./package/foo.c",
            "verifiedUsing": [
                {
                    "algorithm": "SHA1",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "d6a770ba38583ed4bb4525bd96e50461655d2758"
                },
                {
                    "algorithm": "MD5",
                    "comment": null,
                    "hashValue": "624c1abb3664f4b35547e7c73864ad24"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:199e1cae90e1267c66c4cbf4ee18554d",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-File",
            "relationshipType": "DESCRIBES",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-DOCUMENT"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:6dfcfb8208e1ca7e9c70f71711f4a98d",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-Package",
            "relationshipType": "DESCRIBES",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-DOCUMENT"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:60e01b3e7a808f647e10da9d1a410d46",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-Package",
            "relationshipType": "CONTAINS",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-DOCUMENT"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:d8cf621c16adeba0b8b33849f822ef8d",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "DocumentRef-spdx-tool-1.2:SPDXRef-ToolsElement",
            "relationshipType": "COPY",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-DOCUMENT"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:921cefb9906dbfbae3f6460947503881",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-Saxon",
            "relationshipType": "DYNAMIC_LINK",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-Package"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:0e675ef38572f8a8d9b9a89427743c7b",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-CommonsLangSrc",
            "relationshipType": "GENERATES",
            "to": [
                "NOASSERTION"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:1640e87f8c68bb1a9667b6aa9a09fbd1",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-Package",
            "relationshipType": "CONTAINS",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-JenaLib"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:d6ab9c9f7b563885d93708156574f571",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-fromDoap-0",
            "relationshipType": "OTHER",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-Specification"
            ]
        },
        {
            "@type": "Relationship",
            "SPDXID": "urn:Relationship:404aa56714a351411f6ae05952144027",
            "creationInfo": {
                "created": "2010-01-29T18:30:22Z",
                "createdBy": [
                    {
                        "actorType": "TOOL",
                        "name": "LicenseFind-1.0"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "ORGANIZATION",
                        "name": "ExampleCodeInspect ()"
                    },
                    {
                        "actorType": "PERSON",
                        "name": "Jane Doe ()"
                    }
                ],
                "dataLicense": "CC0-1.0",
                "profile": [
                    {
                        "name": "core"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "software"
                    },
                    {
                        "name": "licensing"
                    }
                ],
                "specVer": "3.0.0"
            },
            "from": "SPDXRef-File",
            "relationshipType": "GENERATES",
            "to": [
                "SPDXRef-fromDoap-0"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "name": "SPDX-Tools-v2.0"
}